TRAN TRUNG TRUC

Website: viblo.asia/u/tructt2 GitHub: github.com/trungtruc123 Email: tieuthu.anninh@gmail.com LinkedIn: truc-tran-trung-380533149

Phone: +84 369224293

Experience 2 years with machine learning, deep learning, and applications in Computer Vision, Nature Language Processing, and Speech. Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.

My researches focus on using new Deep Learning techniques to solve Natural Language Processing and Computer Vision problems. I like to write blogs to share knowledge and experience about AI and participate in discussions about new development in AI techniques.

EXPERIENCE

FTECH Co.,Ltd

employees.

Al Engineer 10/2021-present

• Techniques leader for implementing product chatbot to manage the time help for salary payment of

- Techniques leader for implementing product chatbot VAFTECH (https://ftech.ai/).
- Implement tool to clean and transform raw data to input format required by models.
- Builds library for conversation AI platform is among the most advanced AI platforms for building production-quality conversational applications.
- Experience in process building and project management.

FPT Software

Al Engineer 09/2020–09/2021

• Implement projects Object Detection help for recognition error of battery such as foreign objects, bent, cracked, deformation.

- Implement projects Key-point Detection help marker detection of parking car applies to autonomous vehicle systems.
- Generate data use architecture Generative Adversarial Networks help abundant and diverse data.
- Implement application help product reviews on e-commerce websites such as Lazada or Tiki based on comments of customers.
- Implement applications generate poetry (6-8) Viet Nam use model GPT-2.
- Get involved in several seminars about reinforcement learning, optimizers, and transformer for image processing.

FSERVING

Intern AI Engineer 03/2020–05/2020

- Implement virtual dressing room products assisting customers in choosing clothes.
- Implement application web helps Vietnamese handwritten character recognition.
- Approach algorithm about Machine Learning, Deep Learning.

DAC Viet Nam

Developer Python 01/2020–03/2020

- Implement web by framework FLASK and FastAPI.
- Familiar with environment Linux and CUDA.
- Implement web, app recognition skin diseases.

EDUCATION

DA Nang University 2016–2020

Major: Information Technology

SKILLS

- Vision: Object detection, key-point detection, anomaly detection, ...
- NLP: Sentiment Analysis, FAQ, NLU, BERT, GPT-2, ...
- Data Structure, Database: MongoDB, MySQL
- Language: Python, C, Java, JavaScript
- Deployment: Docker, API (Flask, FastAPI), Devops
- Framework: Pytorch, Tensorflow

Scholarships And Awards

University scholarship for talented program students

2017-2018

University scholarship for talented program students

2018-2019

Interests

- Write blogs to share knowledge and experience about AI.
- Participate in a discussion about new development in AI techniques.
- Research new paper to solve Natural Language Processing and Computer Vision problems.